04:00, ma'am.
So...
So, no pyjamas ever?
Ted! Never.
OK.
Georgina!
Georgina.
Quick,
your sister's on the telly.
Victoria, I'm watching you
on the telly and you're great.
Can you call me when you land, please?
I think Jeremy's...
Well, he's... Doing what you
always said he was doing
and now I don't know what to do.
So, call me as soon as you land, please.
So, Victoria, I wonder if I may,
I wanna ask about
something more serious.
Mm-hm.
Let me get you a cup of tea.
Folks, this is
a Cinderella story of tragedy,
resilience, and finally hope.
Take us back, if you will,
Victoria, to that small cottage
with holes in the roof,
holes in the shirts,
your mother was mending to put
a few pennies on the table.
What?
And two great holes
in your family.
Ladies and gentlemen,
both Victoria's father
and stepfather
served their country
as navy pilots.
OK, they won medals together
in the Falklands War in '82.
May we begin with your father?
Yes, my father
is the one on the left,
but he died when
I was only three years old.
His plane suffered
engine failure.
It was a routine exercise.
But then?
Then, after my older sister
Katherine and I lost Daddy,
my beautiful, brave mother
married his best friend.
Also in the fleet air arm,
also called John.
Though we really knew him
as Johnny.
And my little sister Georgina
was born.
But then our second daddy
went missing
in action in Bosnia.
So, by the time you were ten,
you had lost both your father
and your stepfather,
both flying navy planes,
and your mother was left alone,
with three little girls.
Bloody hell.
Now, there's a word
we hear everywhere,
and you just used it Victoria,
but I wonder,
can you define loss to us?
Sorry?
Can you say what loss
means to you?
- Blimey!
- Yes, Cinders. Let's hear that.
It's always there.
And also not there.
I feel that...
But there's a happy ending
this weekend?
There is. As soon
as I leave this studio,
I will be winging my way
back to Blighty,
because my mother, Diana,
is getting married again.
But this time to a man
with his feet
firmly on the ground.
- Victoria Frost, always great...
- Thank you.
To have you here on the show.
The movie's called
The Dame of Darkness 5.
- Four.
- Sorry. Great franchise.
- Ugh.
She's altering, ma'am.
Turning to starboard.
20 degrees. 30.
Off you go.
Turn right for the Baltic.
Back to the motherland.
Permission to
stand down weapon crews, ma'am.
Approved, POO. You can
take over from here, Sean.
Dangerous mission tomorrow.
Got to get my mother down the
aisle and deal with my sisters.
Er, Captain. I'd just like
to take this opportunity
to wish you all the best
on your new command.
Real privilege working for you.
It's been a privilege
for me too, Sean, thank you.
- Onwards.
- Yes, ma'am.
Oh, this bloody country.
Honestly, Victoria.
This is such a mistake.
You didn't have a better idea.
We couldn't get hold of you.
I took command.
I really think you should have
come to me first.
Georgina discovered the texts
on Jeremy's phone.
Then he cancels coming here
tonight.
Well, it's a no-brainer.
We need an intervention.
But hiring a detective?
God's sake.
I'm barely off the plane
and she's ringing me in tears
from her ward because
you were too busy.
And then I saw Steve.
- Who's Steve?
- Right there.
Victoria, let's just wait.
Whatever you may think,
that's a sign. Hello?
This weekend is for
Mum's wedding.
- Victoria?
- Katherine?
Victoria?
Oh, I love this photo.
Christ Almighty. Look at that.
She thinks we're still broke.
Possibly because she heard it
on an American talk show.
All she has to do is ask me.
Oh. Poor little things.
Bloody reception.
No wonder we never visit.
It's the Dark Ages.
Bugger off.
I'll show you mine
if you show me yours?
- No.
- I know who it is anyway.
Oh, for fuck's sake,
he's tried to come.
Who? Where?
- Grand fromage.
- He's still chasing you?
Big cheese.
He's trying to find a place
to land tomorrow.
Oh good.
Steve will be here any minute.
Who's Steve?
The detective.
Oh, God. I hope we catch
bloody Jeremy at it.
She'll get rid of him finally.
Oh, look. Steve! In here.
Where did you find a detective?
AA. What?
No, it's fantastic
for all that sort of thing.
Mm. Plumbers, dentists,
insurance, the lot.
And when Georgie rang me,
I was just getting
to my meeting,
cos I always go as soon
I get to this fucking country.
Bingo.
There was Steve.
Honestly, it was meant to be.
Destiny.
Don't worry. I paid for it all.
So we've hired a drunk
detective.
Come on.
Ex-drunk.
Guess we'll do that.
- Hi.
- Hi, darling.
- Mwah.
- Hi.
Hi, Katherine.
Hi, how are you doing?
Oh, Steve. This is my older
sister, Katherine.
An honour.
Steve was just telling me
all about the cameras
he's set up at home.
It's all a bit complicated.
Yes. I was just telling
the principle client,
by whom in this instance
I mean Georgina,
that I've installed six devices,
all connected via an intranet
with the derived material
saved on the cloud.
Not an easy job, but luckily,
the Taiwanese
do a very good router.
Completely different
to the old Korean one.
And there's this new
Swiss motion detector.
Georgie, are you sure you really
want to go through with this?
My God. That's incredible?
We've got exactly the same
curtains. How funny.
Not sure I can face
watching this tonight.
I wouldn't advise that.
In my experience, our clients,
if they watch proceedings live,
they can get quite violent.
- Oh.
- Especially the English wives.
I'll be back in correspondence
tomorrow.
But for now, if I could just
demonstrate to your good selves
the variety of options you have.
Ooh.
I would suggest, in your case,
the edited highlights package.
It's our best feature.
We've recently got
the musical rights to
"If You Wanna Be My Lover"
by the Spice Girls.
Girls, what are you all
doing in my studio?
Hi.
- Come on, out.
- This is my workplace.
- Hi, Mum.
Hello, darling. Sorry I wasn't
here when you arrived.
Good afternoon.
Oh, you look wonderful.
Hello. We haven't met.
Oh, this is Steve,
he's from my...
He's from my office.
Yes. Er, just doing a bit
of research for Georgina, here.
Oh, well, Steve,
how very accomplished of you
to be so in demand.
Oh, so the marquee is up.
The children are back
from swimming
any minute now. Please make sure
your boys are tidy for dinner.
You know Geoff
will want to leave on time.
Yes. Yes. Yes.
- I'll leave you to it, yeah?
- See you later.
- Take care.
- Bye.
Look, I frankly don't care
if my husband's
shagging half of London.
Tomorrow's Mum's day
and we can't ruin it.
Got your thingy next week, too.
Let's not make
too much of a fuss
about all this, please.
- Mummy. Mummy.
- Hi!
- How was it?
- Hey, Mum.
Mum, look what Stanley got me.
- What have you got there?
- It's a Date With Darkness ring.
It's from my mum's latest movie.
Gotta have one of these babies.
- Sorry, bro.
- It's cool. Don't worry.
It's promo stuff.
I'll get one sent to you.
No, it's fine.
I gotta go home.
Oh, say hi to your dad for me.
Bye, John.
Do we have to go
to Geoff's dinner tonight?
Who goes to their grandpa's
Saturday night?
And watch some eagle
and check out some chicks.
It's an osprey not an eagle,
Skylar.
And Marcus, it's very nice of
Geoff to ask you, OK.
They're extremely rare.
You're very lucky.
And anyway,
he's not your real grandpa.
He's just Granny's new husband.
So, you just press these buttons
and you move forwards.
And you're making him do that?
- Yeah.
- Wow.
Go and play...
Look, Daddy's on the telly.
'Weather conditions have
worsened.
'Police say
the helicopter search
'has been called off for now.
'Commander Munson is married
with three daughters.
'The search will resume
in the morning.'
Keep stirring that, please.
Don't let it burn.
Oh! Sorry, darling.
Don't eat all of that, honey.
Oh, Victoria. Can you take these
through for me?
I called the hotel and warned
them we might be a bit late.
Apparently,
as well as the ospreys,
some great crested grebes
have been sighted,
so we might...
We might get lucky.
Oh, Skylar!
You look wonderful.
So do you, Marcus.
So grown up. So smart.
You shouldn't be here.
It's my hen party.
No men allowed.
Except for the strippergram
we have coming later.
Don't worry, Geoff,
we've got a recyclable one,
so you guys can have him after.
Oh, right.
The lesser crested grebe
is identifiable because his
penis,
that is proportionally
larger than a bonobo's...
Bonobos form same sex
partnerships.
What has happened to our mother?
Why on Earth would she
choose him?
Ooh, I think he looks
rather good.
And he's a nice, kind man
and he makes her happy.
For someone
who hasn't got kids of his own,
he is amazing with my girls.
Anyway, third time lucky.
I mean, bloody hell,
her third husband.
- She's caught up with me.
- Daddy number three.
Two for me.
Well, I say, the more,
the merrier.
OK.
What should I take?
Have we got? Nah, take it.
What was going on with that man?
- Who?
- Steve. Who was he?
Oh...
I would like to propose...
Ding, ding, ding.
- A toast.
- Oh, come on.
Go for it, Georgie.
Right, as the youngest
and the least celebrated
of all your daughters...
By far the prettiest.
Definitely the drunkest.
Anyway, Mummy. Tonight
is your last night as a Munson.
What? You're not gonna
change your name again?
Of course
I'm gonna take Geoff's name.
- Mrs Geoffrey Loveglove?
- Stop it.
Are you serious?
I mean, really?
Yes. Mrs Frost, Mrs Munson,
and now Mrs Loveglove.
Loveglove! No, it's a beautiful
name. It's not his fault.
Well, everyone's always going on
about how brave you were
and how broke you were.
Most recently to promote
the Dame Of Darkness 5.
Four, actually. Thank you.
And I am a widowed goddess.
Ten million Americans think
you were darning socks
by the light of a candle.
But you were amazing.
Three little girls
all on your own.
Anyway, I just wanted to say
how lovely it is
for us all to be here.
- The family together.
- Hear, hear.
Cheers, Mummy.
Oh, my darlings.
To Mummy Loveglove.
To Mummy.
- Hello.
Mm-mm-mm.
The girls are so excited
about being
bridesmaids tomorrow.
- You're OK?
- Yeah.
Yeah, you know, working for the
NHS is not glamorous
and the pay is crap,
but I love it.
- Georgie, you know what I mean.
- You always hated Jeremy.
No, I didn't. Not hated.
I just...
It's my fault.
I shouldn't have looked
at his messages.
Probably just watching Arsenal.
Well, you'll find out tomorrow.
Can I have a puff?
Aw.
It's all right, let it out.
Come here, sweetie.
Come on, my love. I know.
I know. I know.
We're all feeling really
overwhelmed right now.
And you're just like me.
Experiencing real abandonment
issues.
Oh, no.
OK.
Oh, hang on.
So, is the grand fromage
coming tomorrow?
God, I hope not.
He's trying to.
Fucking hell, did you see
what he sent the old bag?
Don't call her that.
Still, it's a luxury holiday.
He owns the hotel.
It's bullshit, Georgie.
He thinks people that will like
him if he gives them things.
And you, er, you know...
Anyway, if I were you
I'd just take the plunge.
I mean, we all know
that the grand fromage
is a bit ancient.
But at least
it's not another drug addict.
Or a total dickhead
like that actor bloke.
What about that boxer?
If you were me, the only men
that are brave enough
to chase you are the arseholes.
Nice ones are too busy
being nice.
They're not interested in going
out with famous actresses.
Well, in that case,
I'd take the money and run.
You'd all take the money
and run.
You're all living vicariously
through me.
That's what my shrink says.
Why does everybody think
I'm so mercenary?
Well, what does your shrink say?
My shrink says I deserve agency.
Agency?
- Yes.
- Bullshit.
I think you are looking
for your father figure.
- That's pretty bloody obvious.
- Charlie's coming tomorrow.
Mm. My brother figure.
Possibly the only man
you should have slept with.
Please. Dream On.
We missed you.
We're good.
Oh, what's going on between
Katherine and Jack, pray tell?
Oh. I do wish you
could stay a bit longer.
Mm. I have a million things
to do. You know that.
Yes, I do.
But you must try and spend more
time with Marcus.
You can't always just leave him
with Jack.
And now this new promotion.
You do realise
that everyone wishes it was
you two getting married tomorrow
- and not me.
- We are happy as it is, Mum.
Oh, rubbish. You may be happy
with the state of affairs
but Jack is not.
I don't know what this
"we're together but not married"
business is.
Sometimes you're away at sea
for months on end.
Well, that's not fair.
I don't know what's going on
between you and Jack,
but I do know that your son...
Your son needs to know
who he belongs to.
Let me just get through this
week, please, Mum.
OK.
I don't know what's wrong...
Yeah?
Sorry.
Can I stay with you for a bit?
Yeah, of course.
Oh-wah!
I can't sleep.
I'm not surprised.
- Georgie...
- Let's not talk about that.
I'm just thinking
about this house.
Do you remember that play
that Victoria was in?
The Chekov one.
The one without the aliens.
To be fair...
- She was great.
- She was.
Sister's trapped in that house.
Chasing ghosts.
No, they wanted to live
but their entire world
revolved around men.
The world's different now.
It's not just about
who you marry.
Why are you so weird about Mum
changing her name?
Oh...
Thank you. 26.
Thank you.
- Thank you, gents. That was fun.
- Mummy!
Oh, they've woken up the girls.
Bye!
Quiet, Ad.
Oh, sorry to wake you.
Oh, my God!
No, no, I'm terribly sorry!
I'm in the wrong room.
Jesus! Geoff!
I do apologise.
Excuse me, Clara.
Oh...
People pay good money
to see this.
Oh!
Do you want to be a Munson,
Katie Frost?
Why don't you think about it
while I'm gone?
Fucking England.
Oh. Hi, Charlie.
Hello, Victoria.
You're up early.
Well, lots to do. Big day.
How've you been?
Do you want to come in,
have a cup of tea?
Oh, no. It's very kind.
But I can't.
I just came to drop
the keys off for Geoff.
I've got Tom in the car.
Oh, you should come in.
Skylar would love to see him.
From what I saw last night,
I reckon Skylar and Marcus
would probably prefer
to stay in bed.
Oh, dear...
Erm... But I'll see you later,
and good luck.
Bye.
Oh, wanker.
Oh, bring me my women!
- Daddy's here!
- Oh-ho-ho. There you are.
Oh, my goodness.
Still in your pyjamas.
Oh, there you go. Take that.
Yeah. Mwah.
Oh, God, I am starving.
Have you had breakfast?
Let's go in. Come on.
What we having?
Come on. Race you.
- Where's Katherine?
- Katherine?
Er, my mum.
Oh, I dunno. Sorry, Marcus.
Mum.
Daddy!
- Yeah?
- Can I borrow your deodorant?
Sure. Yeah.
- Here you go.
- Thanks.
- Pink, orange...
- Skylar.
Oooh, beautiful.
Skylar.
Beautiful.
Constant sun, sun, sun.
Ah, Victoria.
If I could just apologise again
about last night's unfortunate,
er, misunderstanding.
I-I-I didn't see any
of the important bit.
- There you are.
- Behold Jezza's finest.
Oh, yes. Very smart.
Come on, you two.
Give me a hand with this bubbly.
We need to get it
into the marquee.
- Yeah, yeah. Hold up.
- Just finishing.
OK. Well, don't rush.
How was the work dinner?
It was a total bore.
I so wish I could have
been here instead.
OK, well,
don't just stand there.
You're not made of sugar.
Geoffrey, were you really
Aunty Victoria's strippergram?
Well, Clara. I'm retired now,
so chance of a bit
of extra work is always welcome.
Skylar!
- Skylar, why can't you marry us?
- I'm your cousin.
Yeah, but our mummy's only
Aunty Victoria's half sister.
I'm sure it's legal
in Utah, dude.
Ah, shut up.
Watch out. Pass the ball. Mummy!
- Yes?
- Where's Utah?
I don't know, Clara.
Jeremy, do you think you could
ferry people to the church?
In a convertible?
Another brilliant idea
from Georgie Porgie here.
Jesus Christ.
What's Jezza said wrong?
When did you become "Jezza"?
- When he became an asshole.
- What?
Just let's get a move on.
All right. Come on.
Oh, my goodne...
Yep?
- Where can I put these?
- Oh, I'll take them.
Whoa. Bloody hell.
Who ordered these?
Has somebody died?
- Mummy!
- Oh, hello, darling.
Oh, Jack. You made it.
I'm sorry I'm late.
That bloody car.
My handsome grandson.
- Hello stranger.
- You look that good.
Nice to see you.
Are you masturbating already?
Ignore her. Just ignore her.
What's this ring?
Are you keeping drugs in here?
- Bus, Ma.
- Katherine.
Ah, you. You're here.
- Jack's here.
- You're good at engines.
D'you think you could take
a look under my bonnet?
I thought you'd never ask,
Belkis.
My sparkplugs
only answer to you. Please.
Now, where's the blushing bride?
Oh, she's upstairs.
- Oh, Katie.
- Oh, you smell delicious.
I'm coming up, you old slag.
Jack, thank God you're here.
Can you help organise?
We've only got 20 minutes.
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
Erm...
Hey, now, who is an usher?
And where on Earth
can the bridesmaids be?
- Me! Me! Me! Us! Us!
- I can't see anyone.
OK. You wait right here.
This one's for you, love.
Here. Right. Where's the groom?
Groom.
Yes, I'm here, Jack.
I thought I might just walk.
Oh, nonsense, Geoffrey.
You're the star of the show.
You can come with...
You can come with Jeremy in
that groovy little motor of his.
- OK?
- Yeah.
Hey. Oh...
If you want to run,
now is the time.
Try some of this,
it's wonderful.
- What is it?
- CBD.
- God's gift to granny brides.
- Oh, bloody hell.
God. Open the window.
Oh, at least he's not
wearing his shorts.
- What?
- Nothing.
I can't understand you.
Do you absolutely
have to marry him after all
those hotties? I mean, Diana.
Absolutely, yes, I do.
Don't worry.
To be frank,
my worry is the wedding
that's not taking place today.
I know! Do you know,
I said exactly
the same thing to Katherine
last night.
Bloody lesbians. They fight
for the right to get hitched up,
then they never do it.
Seriously.
I'm worried my Jack's moody.
It's not like her at all.
Oh, don't worry.
They'll sort it out.
But you and I should
keep an eye on Marcus.
Ah. We're just
talking about you.
Well, guess Jack and the
boys are waiting for you.
Well, assuming Jeremy Clarkson's
fixed my motor
I'll bugger off to the church.
Chain down Mr Loveglove.
So he can't wriggle out of it.
Good luck.
You and I need a chat,
young lady.
I'm ready.
Oh no. Not you, surely.
- Hmm?
- Do you have to take his name?
Of course.
It's a bit of a funny one.
No. It's not that.
Your name is who you are.
Ah. That's what Johnny Munson
used to say.
But you will always
be my Katie Frost.
Now come on.
You're my rock.
That's mine.
I hope I'm not the only one
wearing a hat.
Please be seated.
Do you, Diana Francis Munson
take Percival Geoffrey Loveglove
to be your lawful wedded
husband?
- I do.
- Percy Loveglove.
Nice one.
You may kiss the bride.
Oh, look, it's sunny.
Woo!
Congratulations, Geoff.
Congrats, Geoff.
See you back there.
Back in mine, yeah?
Granny, Granny, Granny!
I need to talk to you
and Victoria.
Yeah? What's the matter?
I... It's something I should
have told you long ago.
Georgie, Steve's just texted.
He's got something
he wants to show you.
Oh, God.
- Will you both come with me?
- Definitely. Of course.
You can show us
after everybody's left.
I don't think
you should do this here.
Wait till you get back
to London.
No, no. I really want you
to be with me. Really, I do.
Anyway, Katherine,
what did you want to tell us?
Tell us what?
Oh, er, never mind.
Look, there.
Oh, God. No.
That's my bloody field.
Bonjour!
Good lord.
He's almost as old as Geoff.
'Ello. Hope we have not caused
too much of a disturbance.
Jerome, I told you not to come.
I was close by and wanted
to embrace the bride
and bring you this.
- How lovely. Erm...
- Be careful. It's quite heavy.
Erm, well, you're here now.
Stuart, I'm so sorry.
This is Jerome, my dear friend,
and I know he'll reimburse you
for any damage done
to the field.
Absolument, monsieur.
We will fix you right, sir.
- Oui.
- Victoria, how gorgeous you are.
Merci. Welcome.
Lovely to see you.
Come say hi to Mum.
- She's in the marquee.
- OK.
You lucky sod.
I wish the podium would've
landed in one of my crap fields.
Hi guys. Sorry I'm late.
Excuse me, miss.
- Hello. I'm Belkis.
- Jerome.
Nice to meet you.
It's very generous of you
to bring such a large bottle.
Yeah.
Oliver, sit back, please.
Would you like some of this?
Have a little Prosecco.
There we go.
Lovely. Cheers.
Lovely to see you.
I can see by looking
at your mother,
that Victoria will only get
more beautiful with age.
I hope very much
that your sister
will allow me
to take care of her.
She deserves a better life after
all you have been through.
Your family is so tragic.
- Oh.
- I-I mean that in a good way,
Classic. Greek.
You know what I mean.
Like Zeus.
Or Zorba.
Excuse me for asking you,
but are those things safe?
I've never been in a helicopter.
Sorry. What?
You see, my car's being
a bit naughty.
I'm only in Little Hinton.
Hop, skip, and jump
in a helicopter.
But of course.
Erm, only I'm afraid
I will have to leave very soon.
Perhaps too early for you.
No. No. I'm ready.
Theatre or television?
Film mostly.
- For example?
- Dame of Darkness.
Any recent ones?
Who else is in it?
Vicky here is our local star.
Didn't you see her in
Jack and the Beanstalk?
The only reason
that I ever did panto
was because your mum made us.
- Yes.
And you were jealous because
I was a much better fairy
than you.
True. Then you kissed me.
My first.
And your best.
Of course.
But then you kissed Jenny
and you never
looked at me again.
Yeah, well, we were all a bit
fickle at 12.
So, is Napoleon there
your boyfriend?
No. I mean, not decided.
Can you see him at the back
of a pantomime horse?
Then he's not the man
that will make you happy.
Decided.
We've been spotted.
No. No.
Wine is the...
So you two currently
at war or at peace?
Geoff. Marcus and Skylar
were just telling me
about the Ospreys
yesterday evening.
How lucky were you to see them?
Oh, they were magnificent.
To think they've flown
all the way here just to nest.
Rather like you and me.
Yes! Yes!
Irresistibly drawn by the light.
Hmm?
So we're moths to a flame?
Yeah. Yeah,
moths get a back rap.
D'you know they're
extremely clever?
They've got tiny scales on their
wings that allow them
to slip through the most
tightly woven spider's webs.
Hmm.
That's not reassuring, Geoff.
I'm gonna go back.
Hit the gym this morning,
didn't I? Whoa. There we go.
Fantastic.
Unfortunately,
I missed my little brother's
first wedding,
so I'd just like
to begin by saying
that along with Diana's
two Johns
I'm sure his Carol
is watching us from up there,
with a glass of bubbly,
wishing you both every luck.
Here, here.
Now, on with the jokes!
Don't let him off!
I imagine that you might
think that because
Geoff's gonna hang up
his binoculars soon
that I'm gonna give my brother
an easy time.
Mum, how long is this going on?
It'll stop soon, I promise.
One of the larger specimens.
Quick question.
Is it OK if I go to London
tonight with Mummy?
Well, you're going tomorrow,
so I thought
I can go home and then
still see you on Monday.
Oh, look... Stay.
It's just one night.
And Skylar's here.
You have to keep him company.
- OK?
- OK then.
I'm afraid I have to go.
Oh, but you've only just
arrived.
I just want to say that I really
admire what you have achieved.
You did such a great job
raising these wonderful women.
I'm older. Perhaps not as
exciting as her other fiances.
Oh, but I thought
you were still married.
Oui. But we live
very separate lives these days.
Oh, so you want my permission
for my daughter to become
your official, erm, mistress.
Forgive me my cher Diana.
But Victoria now
needs someone who can
bring her comfort
and who's big enough
not to be overwhelmed
by her fame.
I know you will understand that.
At our age, a man finally
understands what he wants.
Ah. Unfortunately,
I must leave now.
But I need you to know
that I want simply the best
for Victoria and the boy.
Your grandson.
Oh, Monsieur Jerome,
as you pointed out,
we are the same age.
So, would you mind if
I were honest with you?
Not at all.
Geoff and I are so touched
by your very generous gift.
But as we did tell everyone
no presents,
we thought it would be
rather nice to donate
your lovely week in the
Seychelles as the price draw
at the church fete.
As long as you don't mind.
But of course, what a good idea.
I get my people onto it.
- Congratulation again, sir.
- Thank you.
I'll see you out.
Well, maybe the Seychelles
wasn't such a good idea?
- Ready?
- Yes. Yes.
Now, everyone.
As you might know,
this bridegroom is not
much of a speechifier.
But if I can fire a phrase,
beau marche.
What's sometimes too difficult
to say in English
can always be sung in French.
This song describes perfectly
how I feel about my bride.
My wife.
My blessing.
Diana Loveglove.
Here we go.
I, er... missed you.
Whaa! Geoff's seen a few
blue tits in his time.
Tim and the boys were cringing.
- Who was he?
- Geoff's brother!
You really are out of it today.
Poor Geoff,
he looked so embarrassed.
Wasn't he was so sweet,
Mummy that song? Oh...
I have to admit having
a bit of a weep.
I didn't know
he could parle Francais.
Oh, Victoria, what was going on
with you and Charlie?
I can see it now.
"Famous actress...
marries childhood sweetheart."
Georgina, I'm going to tell you
one last time.
Do this when you get home.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Let's just get on with it.
- Or don't do it at all.
- No.
I need to know.
Oh, I have taken the liberty
of adding the soundtrack,
I thought it'd provide
context and solace.
No. Sorry.
That's not...
- Just play the bloody thing.
- Yeah. Sure. OK.
Oh, she must be a pro.
Oh! For God's sake,
can we just turn this off?
Erm, actually, I think Georgina
should see a bit more.
Is that...
Is that what I think it is?
Oh, Jezza, you are so screwed.
Argh!
Katherine, let her...
Just leave her.
Fuck.
No!
Oh...
Poor Georgie.
You shouldn't have
done this now.
Poor Jeremy.
Poor Jeremy?
He's a scumbag.
He's a fucking sex addict.
Stop.
- You have got what you wanted.
- What?
I've known he's unfaithful
for years. Of course...
That is... that is like
I don't even know him.
How... How could you?
That's not your fault.
You just don't get it, do you?
Both of you just famous
and beautiful.
- You're so pretty...
- Oh, fuck off, Victoria!
I'm also bloody good
at my job too,
but nobody puts me
on a talk show.
And the one thing...
One thing that made me
more special
'cos the tragic death
of my war hero father,
and even there
you beat me to it.
You lost two fathers.
It's almost my first memory.
Grown ups talking
in hushed voices.
Going, "Poor Georgina."
And somebody else saying,
"Oh, but just think about
Katherine and Victoria."
- Georgie, stop.
- But I did one thing right.
I did one thing better
than both of you.
I committed. I got married.
I had two little girls.
Ordinary, happy little girls.
- And they are happy. They are.
- Yeah.
He was never good enough
for you, George.
No.
Bollocks.
Oh, gosh.
I'm so sorry about your iPad.
I'll pay for another one.
It's all par for the course.
The material, needless to say,
is secured on the cloud.
And I have procured
this copy for you.
Good luck.
You know,
this changes everything.
It's all his.
The house, the money,
but I'm going to sit down
and I'm going to
write it all out.
Every bottom wiped, every
supermarket trolley filled,
every plate washed,
every minutes spent on the phone
to customer care,
every shirt ironed.
And I'm going to bill him for
every penny he has fucking got.
He can move out tomorrow.
And don't worry.
Got my admirers.
If a nice sensible one shows up,
I will try again.
Just like Mummy.
Right. So, that's that.
Katherine,
what did you want to tell us?
I'm... er, not now, Georgie.
It can wait.
No. Now, please.
I've never told either of you
about something
that happened years ago.
Your father, Georgina,
wanted to adopt Victoria and me
and I said no.
He asked if I wanted to change
our names to his.
I wanted to stay
my real daddy's daughter
and remain a Frost.
Why don't you think
about it while I'm gone?
Taking his name
meant dropping Daddy's name.
Betraying him.
I think Johnny understood,
but I know I hurt him.
And of course,
I never saw him again.
I should have told you before.
Well, there you are.
So...
You rejected him.
I didn't understand.
I asked for more time.
Which he didn't have.
I didn't know that then.
I didn't know he was going
to die.
I was only 12 years old.
How have you never
told me this before?
I didn't mean to hide it.
But it was my name too.
It was...
I was a little girl.
Always so fucking secretive.
When I think of the things
that I've told you...
I... I thought we told
each other everything.
What about you, Victoria?
Have you kept your promise
to anyone?
To me or to anyone
in your entire life?
And you didn't even
let Daddy ask me.
Because that's what we called
Johnny Munson, by the way.
Daddy. I repeat,
I was 12 years old.
Well, I would have said yes.
I would have loved
to have taken his name.
When I think "Dad",
I think of him.
Do you know what?
That's it, that settles it.
Every time I come here,
I think it'll be better,
but it never is.
I'm just gonna leave
this shitty little country
and take the Grand Fromage
and all of his money,
and it's gonna be your fault.
There you go again.
Just running off to get
another little man.
Why are you on a high horse?
What you do to Jack.
- Oh, fuck off, Victoria.
- Or your son.
What would Daddy have to say
about that?
Poor little boy.
My father would have
been proud of me.
I am serving his country
and he would have hated the way
you've milked his death.
Tell me, Victoria Frost, of your
numerous successful marriages.
I have never pretended to be
anything but myself.
- Says the famous actress.
- Unlike you.
Did you know about
the pilot in Africa? No?
Georgie, did you hear
about that?
You slept with a man?
Oh, I mean, how could you?
That has nothing to do with it.
And it was a girl. Zoe.
That was it. Zoe.
Zoe in her chopper.
Oh, and I kissed her once, twice.
And she was married.
Zippy Zoe.
Well, at least I never gave
Jeremy a go.
Oh, God. No, Georgie.
It was...
It was years ago.
It was... it was way before
you ever met him.
It was at this stupid party
in London.
I was drunk.
It was way before you ever
appeared with him, Georgie.
Fuck.
That is why you... hate him.
No. No.
That is why you paid for
that video.
You stupid slut.
Oh, God...
Why didn't you just tell me?
I feel sick.
I'm amazed you can remember.
Was it Jeremy the fifth,
or Jeremy the second? Or...
Why do you have
to ruin everything?
God, do you actually care
about anyone at all?
Do you actually love anyone?
You know what, you're right,
Katherine,
I have done some stupid things,
but at least I know
who my son is.
At least I see him.
I don't just dump him
with my girlfriend,
while I go off chugging round
the world trying to be famous.
Come on.
Oh.
I used to leave water on my
feet when I was driving.
I used to have to stop
to change my sock.
Katherine?
- Kate, what's happened?
- Not now, please.
We need to talk.
You never want to talk.
Jack, I cannot make
a decision about us.
I've had a fucking awful day.
I'm pregnant.
What?
I did my research,
found a donor and...
Hang on.
No. No. Just...
Let me finish, OK.
I've never had a child.
Marcus came with you
and I looked after him
since he was tiny.
But this is my baby.
I want it to be ours.
I want you to marry me,
so that you, me, Marcus,
and this child will all grow up
in the same family,
we'll belong to the same family.
I want us have the same name.
Hang on...
When was this?
- I know you love your job.
- Why didn't you ask me first?
Because you're away for months
at a time, Katherine.
Come on!
I've thought about this.
I know you have to travel.
You always have.
But I want this child
to grow up in a proper family
with two parents.
I... I love you, Katherine.
I'm just asking you
to start again with me.
- It was all in my letter.
- Your ultimatum?
Yes. My ultimatum.
That you've never answered.
Possibly never considered.
OK. So this is what it is.
We've been very happy together
for ten years
and now without any warning
you're asking me to give up
my career, my name,
my life, in effect, so I can
co-parent your new child
I never asked for.
If that's how you want
to look at it.
Mummy?
- Yes.
- Oh, hello.
Can Skylar and me
go to Tom's tonight?
Yep, just make sure Victoria's
OK with it.
Yeah. Check with Victoria...
Anyway, I...
You don't want to say anything.
Not even about Marcus?
I know she was only 12,
but she's had all this time
to think about it.
I deserve consideration
because he was...
He was my daddy, too.
Stepdad, but...
I dunno,
I think she's so selfish...
She's selfish.
Oh, everything shipshape?
Pretending that she
knew nothing about it.
It just feels like...
Ew, God...
It just feels like a complete
denial of my existence.
Do you know what I mean?
They just...
they don't even listen.
No-one talks.
No-one says anything
to each other.
They just fumble about.
And now this.
I'm devastated. I'm devastated.
None of them care
about me, really.
They don't take me seriously
as a person.
They think I'm just
some showgirl.
It's like they actually
want me to be some
money-grabbing gold-digger.
Why can't they see me
for what I am?
I'm a person.
That's all we have
time for, I'm afraid, Victoria.
Really?
OK. Thank you.
Same time next week?
Thank you.
- Wait for me.
- Come on. Let's go.
May the ring protect you.
- Where are they going?
- Oh, to Tom's.
- Oh, yeah.
- It's OK. Marcus is fine.
I gave him my torch and he's got
his head on his shoulders.
You all right, Katherine?
- Yeah.
- You've got a lot on your plate,
but you can stop worrying
about one thing now.
Your mum is my job now.
Protecting her, loving her.
That's what I'm here for.
That's why my heart beats.
Good night, Katherine.
God bless Mummy.
God bless Daddy.
Keep him safe.
Skylar, honey.
What's going on?
You're not in any trouble.
Just come down. Skylar, honey.
Come down from that tree!
I think someone's been overdoing
the vodka Red Bull.
My son does not drink, Jeremy.
What the hell is he doing?
It's four in the morning.
He said he wanted to test
the ring.
So he climbed the tree.
See if it works.
Oh, no. Really?
Just talk to me, sweetie.
Just talk to me!
Please say something!
I just want to stay here
for a while.
Why can't you all just chill?
- Uh, I'll get the ladder.
- No, I tried. It's broken.
Who called the fucking police?
No. It's the fire brigade.
I called them.
It's what you do.
Oh, my God.
Skylar, please come down.
Please.
Here we go, fella.
He's up there.
Oh, I see. Might not need
the small harness, boys.
Yeah. Hello, Graham.
I do apologise.
Don't worry, Mr Loveglove.
We've seen worse.
- Skylar, come down.
- Are you filming?
Can you stop filming me, please?
See what's happening here?
- He's filming me!
- I'm sure it's fine.
It's regulations, ma'am.
It's for health and safety.
Don't be ridiculous.
I've heard that before.
- When's he coming down?
- Ask Mr Loveglove.
Well, erm...
Georgina, for God's sake,
can you just get your children
out of here, please?
Thank you, Victoria. Come on.
Oh, just...
- Careful, son.
- You got it.
- That's it.
- This is really alarming now.
- Whoa! Oh!
- Careful, son.
Ooh-ho!
Why, honey? Why?
Stars are beautiful, but they
don't take part in anything.
They just look on forever.
What the fuck?
Second to the right,
straight on till morning.
You're the best of us, man.
Best of this family.
How could you talk about me
like that?
Actually, Victoria,
I think that was from Peter Pan.
We'll talk about it
in the morning.
Did you make him drink?
Would you do that?
Why call the fire brigade?
Why humiliate me like that?
Well, that's what you do when
someone's stuck up a tree.
You call the fire brigade.
He's 14. He's not four.
He'll understand children
because he's never had any.
How dare you!
This is my wedding.
And you,
all three of you,
you will pull yourselves
together.
I don't care what you get up to
in your own homes,
but in my house you will behave
and respect the man
I have just married.
I will be going to the graves
in the morning at ten as usual.
And you will all come with me
and explain what is going on.
I have to leave at ten.
Fine, 9:30 then.
Come on.
I've got it all on camera.
Have a look at this.
Hello. You're up early.
How's Skylar?
He'll be OK.
We crashed at Tom's.
- What on Earth was he doing?
- I dunno.
He said he just wanted to climb
the tree, test the ring.
Honestly.
You were very good with him.
Come here.
What time are you leaving?
Ten.
Geoff was saying there's some
giant puffballs past the bridge.
We have been mushrooming
for ages.
Do you want come for a hunt?
Just you and me.
God, I'm sorry.
I'd love to, but Granny wants us
to go with her to the graves
before she goes on her
honeymoon.
Next time, I promise.
Don't worry,
Geoff will come with me.
When you leave-leave,
I want to see it.
We sail on Tuesday.
Oh, yeah.
I meant to say...
You're in the newspaper.
Geoff went into town to get it.
Er, not like that, thank you.
No.
- Do you want some more toast?
- Yep.
Oh. Ahoy, sailor.
Her car is coming
to pick her up.
Oh, Katherine, look.
First woman to command
a British aircraft carrier.
It's on the front page.
"The Royal Navy has announced
that Captain Katherine Frost
"will make history when she
takes command
"of HMS Prince of Wales at an
official ceremony tomorrow.
"Captain Frost's sister,
the actress Victoria Frost,
et cetera, et cetera.
"Captain Frost's war hero
father, Lieutenant Colonel..."
I think we know the rest.
Come on then. Let's go.
Well, what have you got
to say for yourselves?
Hmm?
Well, I think all three of us
should apologise to you...
- Oh, yeah.
- And to them.
- Yeah, sorry.
- Sorry.
And why... why would you
apologise to them?
Huh?
I brought you up to be women.
Not... not just daughters.
I scrimped and saved and pushed
so that you could build lives
in a way that a young
single mother
with three little girls
never could.
Where did you get this idea
that nobody is as good
as your perfect fathers? Hmm?
They were at sea
most of the time I was married.
I barely saw them.
He missed your birth, Victoria.
I don't know whether either
of my marriages
would have lasted.
And your father, Georgina,
he drove me mad with his...
With his penny pinching,
and oh my God, was he snobbish?
Always telling me
I'd said the wrong thing.
Done the wrong thing.
Sometimes I had.
Johnny Munson wanted me
to change your name to his
because he thought
Frost was too ordinary.
I was too much of a coward
to say no,
so I sent him to you, Katherine,
because I knew that you
would say no for me.
And you...
you have the least excuse.
You know what
young officers are like.
Your tales of mushroom picking
with Daddy. Think about it.
He was probably just
keen to wear out a hangover.
Your fathers were not
the perfect men you imagine.
Hmm.
That you've... you've...
you've...
fantasised about
all these years.
Yes, they were brave young men
who gave their lives
for their country, but they were
still just young men,
doing all the things
that young men do.
Didn't stop me from loving them.
Desperately.
And by God, did they love you.
But you lot have
never ever let go of them.
You are all still a little girls
madly in love with your daddies.
Separate from them.
Just as you did with me.
No, we didn't.
That's what you're supposed
to do.
That's what Skylar was doing
last night. Growing up.
All three of you are older than
these poor boys ever were.
You lot have to live for now.
Live for the living,
for God's sake.
You're all grown women with
your own sons and daughters.
And marriages.
I just always felt like there
was some part of me missing.
Some vital organ.
But you don't have to jump
into bed with every...
Every idiot who possesses one.
Or let that ridiculous man
try and buy you.
- Hmm?
- Mmm.
Or you, Georgina.
Allowing yourself
to be trampled on
like some... some doormat.
Mum!
Or you, treating Jack
like a glorified babysitter.
No, look,
I'm not saying it's easy.
Our entire lives
are about choices.
I know you all think Geoff is
dull compared with these...
these two demigods here.
But he is the man I love.
He makes me happy.
And he cares for me.
Which when you all
eventually grow up,
you will learn
is the most important thing.
So don't you dare blame
the past.
And these poor lost boys.
Let go of the children you were,
and pay attention
to the children, you have.
Hmm?
Because, as you so thoughtfully
reminded us, Victoria,
some of us don't have
that privilege.
Er, I just want to say
your car's here.
Oh.
Thank you, Mum.
I'm so sorry, Geoff.
Muwah.
Thank you for that.
I'm so sorry.
About what?
Last night, I was just...
Didn't do me any harm.
I didn't want you to see that.
Come and have a cup of coffee.
Skylar's sleeping it off
at my house.
Look, we've all
behaved badly at times.
I remember doing a particularly
debauched phase in my youth
wanting to go out with a girl
called Victoria,
kissing a girl call Jenny.
Depths of depravity.
Maybe I just did it
in the wrong order.
Call Napoleon.
Tell him there's been
a terrible mistake.
I'm serious.
Geoff says it's three times
as big as a destroyer.
- Very impressive, right?
- Yeah.
I wish we could have
spent more time together.
But I'll show you everything
tomorrow.
OK.
I've got you two presents.
- Calvatia gigantea.
- Wow!
Quite safe. Tom's really well up
on mushrooms.
What's this?
Oh, it's the ring.
The one Skylar got me.
It gives you superhuman powers.
Wards off danger.
Except for tall trees
and cheap vodka.
- I love you.
- I love you, too, Mum.
- I'll see you tomorrow.
- OK.
- Right, you in the back.
- Aw!
Let's get a belt on.
Thank you. Right.
Good morning, ma'am.
Good to see you, Chris.
Shall we get going?
The extra stripe suits you,
ma'am.
Good to see you, Katherine.
Everything is all set for
tomorrow.
Yes. All this fuss
is a bit ridiculous.
Well, that's the age we live in.
Have a look around.
I'll keep out of the way.
And Chris and Ndidi
will look after you.
There we go.
Come on. Come on.
There we go. There we go.
Oh, watch Mummy. There we go.
Hi, darling.
Oh, God, that drive
is a bloody nightmare.
I think it is time
for a stiff drink,
don't you think?
OK. Come on, girl,
out of my way.
Here are your car keys.
Oh, Jezza's been
a naughty boy again?
And this is what
you were doing here,
in your daughters' home,
on Friday night.
I've put up with your behaviour
for years, Jeremy,
but this is too much.
You need help.
This game is one you can watch
at your leisure.
Georgie.
- Darling.
- Mm-hmm.
- You don't understand.
- Oh.
You're crazy.
What the fuck are you
talking about?
There is nothing to talk about.
There's a letter for you
on the front seat.
It's pretty generous.
Now bugger off, Jeremy.
- Words I choose carefully.
- I...
Georgie. Georgie. Georgie.
This is ridiculous.
Georgie, open the door.
Oh, what's the point?
- All done, ma'am?
- Yes, thank you, Jones.
I found this. I thought you'd
like it for your sea cabin.
Oh, yes. I do. Appreciated.
- How was the mess dinner?
- They're still at it, ma'am.
The helicopter guys
have arrived.
Ah, I see.
Well, that will be all
for today, Jones.
I'll get a quick breath of air.
Wow!
I'm only going to give you
one piece of advice.
Savour every bloody minute.
It'll never get better
than this.
Good luck, Captain Frost.
You ready?
Yes, I am.
Ship's company. Hold.
Ship's company
will remove headdress.
Remove...
headdress.
Three cheers for Captain Frost.
- Hip-hip...
- Hooray!
Ship's company
will replace headdress.
Replace...
headdress.
Ship's company stand at ease.
Good afternoon,
HMS Prince of Wales.
My name's Katherine Frost.
And today's the proudest day
of my life.
Serving this ship,
serving the nation,
doing my duty.
The Royal Navy is why
my heart beats.
There's been a big fuss about
being the first female
to command a ship of this class.
Well...
That's just noise.
What matters most
is what we do now together,
as a team.
And I'm determined,
we will be a successful ship.
- Well done, you.
- Yeah.
Excuse me. Can we get a picture?
Perhaps with your sister?
Thank you. No, not today.
I'm off duty.
Girls. Girls.
You see that chap over there,
talking to Geoff?
That's Perky Perkins.
He taught your fathers.
They absolutely worshipped him.
They used to fly together.
Perky and Frost.
You see, age catches up
with us all.
Take a good look, hmm.
Perky.
We couldn't leave without saying
thank you to the captain.
- Aw...
- I'm so proud of you.
Mwah. Oh, you are an
extraordinary girl.
- Thank you.
- Call me.
Bon voyage, big sis.
Full steam ahead.
Bye, Katie. Well done.
Dad would have been so proud
of his daughter today.
Thank you.
Come on. Ah...
See you're wearing the ring?
Yes, I thought
I'd give it a try.
It's working quite well.
I'm going to miss you, my boy.
- Catch you up, sweetheart.
- OK. Love you, Mum.
Well done, Katie.
This is quite something.
Thank you for coming.
I was worried you wouldn't.
I couldn't of done any
of this without you.
Don't thank me.
I've watched you.
You belong here.
Yes, I do belong here.
It's in my blood.
I can't give it up.
That little boy is growing up
so fast.
He belongs to us.
You and me.
Look...
I'm sorry. I should have
told you sooner.
No. I should have answered
your letters,
picked up the phone.
I owe you everything.
Marcus. My job. My happiness.
Now it's your turn.
You see. Frost is melting.
The Frost is melting.
I love you.
We'll talk more tonight,
before we sail.
Yes.
The bridge is ready for you,
ma'am.